CHRISTINA XAMIN

CONTACT

xaminc@sheridancollege.ca



(416)-523-3132



www.christinaxamin.com

2232 Wuthering Heights Way Oakville, ON, Canada L6M 0A3

SKILLS

- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite
- Confident working with both Macs and PCs, as well as their accompanying software (Microsoft Office, iWork, etc.)
- Understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Excels in use of social media outlets (including Twitter, Instagram, Facebook, YouTube. Pinterest and Tumblr)
- Ability to work in a team with a wide range of people
- Able to make decisions and work through problems
- Manages time effectively
- · Easily adapts to new situations
- · Presents ideas and opinions in an open and unbiased way

CERTIFICATIONS

• CPR Level C + AED

Ambitious designer with 4+ years experience in a professional design environment. Currently working towards a Bachelor of Interaction Design degree. Highly proficient in graphic design. video editing and web design software. Background in visual and creative arts using both traditional and digital elements.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Interaction Design Sheridan College

September 2014- Present

Creativity and Creative Problem Solving Certificate Sheridan College

September 2014 - Present

Visual and Creative Arts Advanced Diploma Sheridan College

January 2012 - May 2014

EXPERIENCE

SOCIAL MEDIA/ DIGITAL BRANDING INTERN **Crowell Lane Creative, New York, NY (Remote position)** May 2016- September 2016

- Designed and researched social media content for brands
- Worked with team to develop promotional campaigns

GRAPHIC DESIGN ASSISTANT (CONTRACT) Oakville Public Library, Oakville, ON

May 2016- August 2016

- · Created various promotional material for print, web and environmental applications
- Maintained a graphic consistency by adhering to the library's visual identity and AODA compliancy
- Provided branding and graphic support for the 2016 TD Summer Reading Program.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER (CONTRACT) AFL Canada, Toronto, ON

November 2013- March 2014

- Designed Men and Women's International Cup jerseys
- · Created design mockups catered towards clients needs